What did you come up with? Let’s talk through
this code and find and fix the two problems
with the code. First, for the print statement on
line 7 to display, the score must be over 10,000,
and the coin needs to be gold or platinum. The
first problem exists on line 5, and it’s a common
problem. The app's logic should dictate that once
someone reaches a score of 10,000, the person
could be on level 2 or 3. But, the logic on line 5
is only looking for scores over 10,000. The common
problem with this code is that people often say,
“Well, if they are over 10,000, do this,” when
they really mean, “If they are at or over 10,000,
do this.” When someone tells you this logic, you
may need to clarify if they mean that the amount
they want to use as a condition includes the exact
amount. In many cases, the condition will include
the exact amount. Thus, we want to change the
comparison on line 5 to greater than or equal.
I will make that change and rerun the code. The
result is different, but note that we do not quite
get the result we are looking for. We are about to
see the example I said you would need to think
through, at least possibly. The coin is gold,
as we see on line 2, but look at the casing here
compared to the if statement on line 6. Though
the word is the same, Python is treating these
as two different values because one is lowercase
and the other is title case. The lesson here is
that Python criteria are case-sensitive. Thus,
I will change the criterion on line 2 to
capital G Gold and rerun the code. Now,
the code works as intended. Get practice analyzing
code line by line, as learning how to analyze code
will help you for the exam and help you greatly
in figuring out and troubleshooting code.